module.exports = [
  {
    question:
      "In which movie do Ryan Gosling and Rachel McAdams play the lead roles?",
    correctAnswer: "The Notebook",
    wrongAnswers: ["The Lucky One", "The Vow", "Dear John"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which romance won the most Oscars?",
    correctAnswer: "Titanic",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The English Patient",
      "Shakespeare In Love",
      "Breakfast at Tiffany's",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Audrey Hepburn and Gregory Peck as two people who fall in love in Rome?",
    correctAnswer: "Roman Holiday",
    wrongAnswers: ["Sabrina", "Breakfast at Tiffany's", "Funny Face"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is based on the Jane Austen novel of the same name and stars Keira Knightley as the lead actress?",
    correctAnswer: "Pride and Prejudice",
    wrongAnswers: ["Emma", "Sense and Sensibility", "Persuasion"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who plays the lead role of Jamie Sullivan in the movie "A Walk to Remember"?',
    correctAnswer: "Mandy Moore",
    wrongAnswers: ["Emma Stone", "Reese Witherspoon", "Jennifer Lawrence"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is about a young couple who fall in love despite belonging to different social classes?",
    correctAnswer: "Dirty Dancing",
    wrongAnswers: ["Romeo and Juliet", "Titanic", "The Notebook"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Julia Roberts and Richard Gere as the lead actors?",
    correctAnswer: "Pretty Woman",
    wrongAnswers: ["Notting Hill", "Runaway Bride", "My Best Friend's Wedding"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is about a woman who falls in love with a soldier during World War II?",
    correctAnswer: "Pearl Harbor",
    wrongAnswers: ["Atonement", "The English Patient", "The Notebook"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Emma Stone and Ryan Gosling as struggling artists who fall in love?",
    correctAnswer: "La La Land",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Crazy Stupid Love",
      "The Big Sick",
      "The Fault in Our Stars",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is about a woman who has to choose between two men who love her?",
    correctAnswer: "The Choice",
    wrongAnswers: ["The Notebook", "Bridget Jones's Diary", "The Holiday"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who plays the lead role of Allie Hamilton in the movie "The Notebook"?',
    correctAnswer: "Rachel McAdams",
    wrongAnswers: ["Amanda Seyfried", "Emma Stone", "Kate Winslet"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Channing Tatum and Rachel McAdams as two people who fall in love, but face obstacles due to a car accident?",
    correctAnswer: "The Vow (2012)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Lucky One (2012)",
      "Dear John (2010)",
      "Safe Haven (2013)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is about a woman who falls in love with her best friend, but he is engaged to someone else?",
    correctAnswer: "My Best Friend's Wedding (1997)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Notting Hill (1999)",
      "Love Actually (2003)",
      "Sleepless in Seattle (1993)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What movie tells the story of a forbidden love affair between a wealthy woman and a poor man aboard a doomed ship?",
    correctAnswer: "Titanic (1997)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Notebook (2004)",
      "A Walk to Remember (2002)",
      "The Fault in Our Stars (2014)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the movie where Julia Roberts plays a prostitute who falls in love with a wealthy businessman played by Richard Gere?",
    correctAnswer: "Pretty Woman (1990)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Notting Hill (1999)",
      "The Notebook (2004)",
      "A Walk to Remember (2002)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Emma Stone and Ryan Gosling as struggling artists in Los Angeles who fall in love while pursuing their dreams?",
    correctAnswer: "La La Land (2015)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Crazy, Stupid, Love (2011)",
      "The Fault in Our Stars (2014)",
      "Me Before You (2016)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the movie where a wealthy businessman, played by Hugh Grant, falls in love with his housekeeper, played by Andie MacDowell?",
    correctAnswer: "Four Weddings and a Funeral (1994)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Maid in Manhattan (2002)",
      "Notting Hill (1999)",
      "Love Actually (2003)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is about a couple who meet on a train and fall in love, but are separated by circumstances, only to reunite years later?",
    correctAnswer: "Brief Encounter (1945)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Time Traveler's Wife (2009)",
      "Before Sunrise (1995)",
      "The Adjustment Bureau (2011)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does a wealthy New Yorker, played by Reese Witherspoon, start dating a man from the south, played by Josh Lucas, but then face opposition from her upper-class family?",
    correctAnswer: "Sweet Home Alabama (2002)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Lucky One (2012)",
      "The Notebook (2004)",
      "Dear John (2010)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the movie where a young woman, played by Amanda Seyfried, travels to Italy to find love and ends up falling for two men?",
    correctAnswer: "Letters to Juliet (2010)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Lucky One (2012)",
      "Dear John (2010)",
      "The Vow (2012)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Keanu Reeves and Sandra Bullock as two strangers who fall in love through a series of mysterious letters?",
    correctAnswer: "The Lake House (2006)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Serendipity (2001)",
      "Sleepless in Seattle (1993)",
      "You've Got Mail (1998)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does a young woman, played by Mandy Moore, fall in love with a bad boy, played by Shane West, while dealing with personal struggles?",
    correctAnswer: "A Walk to Remember (2002)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Lucky One (2012)",
      "Dear John (2010)",
      "The Notebook (2004)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Vow" (2012), what causes Paige to lose her memory?',
    correctAnswer: "A car accident",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "A sports injury",
      "A medical condition",
      "A fall from a horse",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "Dirty Dancing" (1987), what is the name of the resort where Frances "Baby" Houseman goes with her family for vacation?',
    correctAnswer: "Kellerman's Resort",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Mountain Lake Lodge",
      "Grand Hotel Pupp",
      "The Plaza Hotel",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Best of Me" (2014), who plays the adult version of Dawson Cole?',
    correctAnswer: "James Marsden",
    wrongAnswers: ["Josh Duhamel", "Liam Hemsworth", "Ryan Gosling"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the lead role in the movie "The Time Traveler\'s Wife" (2009)?',
    correctAnswer: "Rachel McAdams",
    wrongAnswers: ["Anne Hathaway", "Kate Winslet", "Natalie Portman"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the lead role of Holly in the movie "Breakfast at Tiffany\'s" (1961)?',
    correctAnswer: "Audrey Hepburn",
    wrongAnswers: ["Grace Kelly", "Elizabeth Taylor", "Marilyn Monroe"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Fault in Our Stars" (2014), what is the name of the male lead character?',
    correctAnswer: "Augustus",
    wrongAnswers: ["Isaac", "Peter", "Jacob"],
  },
];
